globalgraphics.com 2017-07-30

# Global Graphics :: Privacy

Global Graphics Software Limited (hereinafter "Global Graphics") is committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with this online privacy policy as amended from time to time (“Privacy Policy”). Global Graphics will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).

Global Graphics collects information about you for two reasons: firstly, to process any orders and secondly, to provide you with the best possible service.

The type of information we will collect about you includes:

  * your name
  * address
  * phone number
  * email address
  * employer
  * job title
  * product interest

We use the information to handle orders, deliver products and services, update our records and generally maintain your account with us. We also use this information to keep you informed about new products, upgrades, and services available from Global Graphics, to improve our on-line store, and prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website. We may also pass on information to our Distributor/Reseller and Corporate Licensing Center partners for market research purposes, so that they may contact you about a potential sales lead, or provide you with the product or service that you require.

## Changes in Privacy Policy

Global Graphics may change its Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and will provide notice of changes on this page. If as a result of such changes you want to alter the ways in which Global Graphics is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by emailing [privacy-information@globalgraphics.com](mailto:privacy-information@globalgraphics.com).

To ensure that your data is secure during transmission we will use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) when you provide us with password or order information.

The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing [privacy-information@globalgraphics.com](mailto:privacy-information@globalgraphics.com). If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct the information promptly.

When you visit this Site your visit to each page is recorded in a log file. This log file records information regarding your domain name and IP address. This information is collected to monitor and analyse traffic to the Site and not for collecting personal information about you.

We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our Site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. We will not pass on your details to third parties, unless expressly stated herein. We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent.

The Site and the products and services are intended for adult audiences, and Global Graphics does not knowingly collect any personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

Global Graphics is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Global Graphics sites to which this website might link.

If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should email [privacy-information@globalgraphics.com](mailto:privacy-information@globalgraphics.com).

Global Graphics Software Limited (hereinafter "Global Graphics") is committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with this online privacy policy as amended from time to time (“Privacy Policy”). Global Graphics will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).

Global Graphics collects information about you for two reasons: firstly, to process any orders and secondly, to provide you with the best possible service.

The type of information we will collect about you includes:

  * your name
  * address
  * phone number
  * email address
  * employer
  * job title
  * product interest

We use the information to handle orders, deliver products and services, update our records and generally maintain your account with us. We also use this information to keep you informed about new products, upgrades, and services available from Global Graphics, to improve our on-line store, and prevent or detect fraud or abuses of our website. We may also pass on information to our Distributor/Reseller and Corporate Licensing Center partners for market research purposes, so that they may contact you about a potential sales lead, or provide you with the product or service that you require.

## Changes in Privacy Policy

Global Graphics may change its Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and will provide notice of changes on this page. If as a result of such changes you want to alter the ways in which Global Graphics is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by emailing [privacy-information@globalgraphics.com](mailto:privacy-information@globalgraphics.com).

To ensure that your data is secure during transmission we will use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) when you provide us with password or order information.

The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing [privacy-information@globalgraphics.com](mailto:privacy-information@globalgraphics.com). If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct the information promptly.

When you visit this Site your visit to each page is recorded in a log file. This log file records information regarding your domain name and IP address. This information is collected to monitor and analyse traffic to the Site and not for collecting personal information about you.

We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our Site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. We will not pass on your details to third parties, unless expressly stated herein. We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent.

The Site and the products and services are intended for adult audiences, and Global Graphics does not knowingly collect any personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

Global Graphics is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Global Graphics sites to which this website might link.

If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should email [privacy-information@globalgraphics.com](mailto:privacy-information@globalgraphics.com).
